ztrenz.com 2015-11-17

# Digital Agency India - Privacy Policy | ZTRENZ

Each of our clients is different and each one has specific needs and each one has a different time frame. Sometimes we get very little time to create a winning strategic plan for your brand and some time it consumes more time than expected as we are flexible we expect the same without clients too. We do understand you have specific dates, events to avail the opportunity of winning more customers and we respect your vision that’s why we’ve a plan too in order to meet our clients expectations and beliefs.

### Opt-In

We use opt-in system that allows us to store non-personally identifiable information about your Internet visits.

ZTRENZ system act intelligently even if you opt-in, and you have opted-out in past, our system quickly detect and remove the opt-out cookies displaying that it is fine for us to store your non-personally identifiable information.

Please note that if you intentionally or unintentionally remove, delete, block or simply restrict cookies, or in case you use a different computer or Internet browser, you may need to renew your opt-in choice.

### Opt-Out

We use opt-out system that allows us to store non-personally identifiable information about your Internet visits.

When you choose to opt-out ZTRENZ intelligent system quickly detect and place an opt-out cookie on your computer. The opt-out cookie advises us not to store your non-personally identifiable information.

Please not that if you intentionally or unintentionally remove, deletes, block or simply restrict cookies, or in case you used a different computer or Internet browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice.

### Type of Information

We collect name, email address, phone numbers, IP address, and message content.

We also collect street, city, state, and zip/ pin codes from you.

### Use of Collected Information

ZTRENZ.com also requires your consent that your provided email addresses on the get in touch section or Reseller section of the website or any email of ZTRENZ.com will be utilized to respond to your question(s) by email. You have the option of also providing information regarding your name, demographics (such as your state and country of residency), operating system, browser, Internet service provider (“ISP”), connection type and email program that you are using.

ZTRENZ.com also automatically receives and records information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP Address and the page you requested. Your IP address is not linked to your email address or ZTRENZ.com.

In certain sections of this website, we require your personally identifiable information, in order to be able to use that particular section or those sections of this website. For example, the names and contact information of persons who visit our Web sites are added to our database so that, for example, they may be contacted in the future regarding ZTRENZ.com products, services, solutions or future opportunities and promotions. Such contact may occur by email, telephone or mail, as ZTRENZ.com thinks right.

### The Purpose of Collected Information

To contact you about the ZTRENZ.com range Services or the Site.

To notify you when you receive a ZTRENZ.com email message.

To communicate with you concerning problems or malfunctions you report.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We do and will not sell or rent any of your personal identifiable information except Law department.

Your information will be shared with our employees, vendors/ suppliers and 3rd party software and service providers. This is mainly related to the project work.

We do not take any guarantees and warrantee behalf of them. As the 3rd party Privacy Policy may vary from ours. So you are please advised to check their Privacy Policy.

Please check 3rd party or advertisers Privacy Policy.

We take utmost care and often email to inform our Resellers, vendors and suppliers about any specific requests from our clients, agencies and companies to take care of their privacy.

 **Note:** We make every sincere effort to make sure about your Privacy especially the financial information; patented material and we do respect your Trademarks and copyrighted material.

### Cookies

When you request some specific services from us, ZTRENZ.com may then attempt to set cookies on your computer and later access those cookies. You can normally refuse cookies by setting preferences in your browser. You do not need to accept cookies in order to use the ZTRENZ.com services and solutions.

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes a unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a Web site’s computers and then stored on your computer’s hard drive. A cookie cannot obtain information from your hard drive, destroy files, or transmit viruses.

ZTRENZ.com may use both “session ID cookies” and “persistent cookies.” ZTRENZ.com uses session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate the Site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie enables ZTRENZ.com to track and target the interests of users to enhance the experience on the website.

Each web site can send its own cookie to your browser, if your browser’s preferences allow it. To protect your privacy, your browser normally only permits a Web site to access cookies that it has previously sent to you, but not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

We do not take or accept any kind of responsibility of 3rd parties or 3rd party software, applications, advertisers, vendors, suppliers, link partners may use cookies on their website. ZTRENZ.com has no access and control over these cookies and in any circumstances ZTRENZ.com is not responsible of any kind of loss whether it is financial or personal.

### Choices about Cookies

You can normally configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.)

If you reject all cookies, you will still be able to use the ZTRENZ.com Services.

Cookies are used only as an option selected by you that allows us to recall your email address from the cookie that we sent to your computer.

### Log Files

When a Web page on the Site is requested, that request (including the date and time) is recorded on our servers with information including the IP address of the computer that requested the page.

ZTRENZ.com uses log files for debugging and troubleshooting reasons. IP addresses and access times are not linked to your email address or any other personally identifiable information.

### Legal Disclaimer

We may reveal your personal information when needed by law or in the good-faith trust that such act is essential in order to conform to the requirements of law or comply with legal activity served on the website.

In any circumstances ZTRENZ.com is not liable for any loss by using pages and the website.  
You have given your consent while you browse the website and access the other pages of the website you have accepted and clearly understand our terms of use and the privacy policy.

### Minors

None of our services or any portion is directed towards minors (which is less than 18 years of age) and we do not expressively ask any information about minors or market to minors.

### Security

Your privacy is our top most priority. We take every possible precaution to protect our users’ information. All collected information on the websites is covered by this privacy policy and it is stored in our secured database. However, no security system is safe. That’s why can’t guarantee the safety of our database, nor can we guarantee that information will not be captured while being transmitted to us over the Internet.

If you have questions regarding the security of ZTRENZ.com website, please e-mail at: support@ztrenz.com and mention privacy policy in subject line.

### Notification of Changes

ZTRENZ.com may alter and amend this privacy policy from time to time. If we make any sizable changes, we will inform you by posting a prominent announcement on ZTRENZ.com.

### Business Relationships

Our websites include links to other websites. Please be aware that ZTRENZ.com has no control or influence over the privacy practices of other websites nor is it responsible for the privacy practices or content of such sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave this site and to read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personal identifiable information.

### Enforcements

If users have questions or complaints with respect to the principles summarized in this privacy statement or enforcement of this privacy statement they must contact:

www.ZTRENZ.com  
3 – 3B, Saket Nagar.  
BHOPAL. M.P. INDIA.  
Pin: 462024
